Narendra Singh

UX/UI Designer

CAREER SUMMARY

UX Professional with 3+ years experience in e-learning and IT for B2B and B2C products with a passion to constantly rethink existing norms in the indsutry. At EdAider, led the design of a learning analytics platform. The MVP helped secure a grant of 1M SEK from Vinnova and later multiple schools as paying customers.

WORK EXPERIENCE

EdAider, Stockholm - Product Designer NOV 2019 - JUL 2020

- MVP design leading to a semester pilot study with a school.
- Developed remote working guidelines to exponentially increase efficiency in a newly formed startup.

Etttak AB, Stockholm - UX Designer

FEB 2019 - JUN 2019

• Research project for a 360° video VR in the rental market opening up remote capabilities.

Pagalguy, Mumbai - UX / UI Designer

DEC 2015 - SEP 2017

• Reached paid course registrations to 100+ in 3 months at Prepathon, a course aggregator platform (now <u>Oheyo.com</u>).

Infosys, Bengaluru - Test Engineer IUN 2014 - NOV 2015

Additionally, I have worked on several freelance projects in UX/UI design under the DeviantDesigner name in my free time.

PORTFOLIO

Design: https://www.deviantdesigner.com

Medium articles (design): https://medium.com/@3 2 1 design

EDUCATION

MS Human-Computer Interaction (Minor in Innovation and Entrepreneurship) EIT Digital - KTH, Stockholm

AUG 2018 - AUG 2019

MS Human-Computer Interaction (Minor in Innovation and Entrepreneurship) EIT Digital - Université Paris Saclay, Paris

SEP 2017 - AUG 2018

+46 793049286

E: <u>narendra0014@gmail.com</u> https://deviantdesigner.com

SKILLS

User research (qualitative and quantitative methodologies), Journey maps, Usability testing, Visual design, Mobile design patterns, Sketch, Figma, Invision, Prototyping, Agile, Typography, Data Visualizations, Accessible design, Business strategy, HTML5, CSS3, Javascript

OTHER EXPERIENCE

Mentor for "Girls in ICT" workshop

Mentor for the cleanup project the city of Södertajle

LANGUAGES

Fluent English, Hindi Intermediate French Elementary Swedish

PUBLICATION

HCI Research Project
Developing Trust in Sharing
Rental Economy through
Virtual Reality 360° Video

Available at KTH Diva Portal